Guide to the Gerard Malanga Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2006 acquisition, 1906-2005; 81.05; (102 boxes) + 2 art, 6 rolls, 4 broadside folders
  - "J. Franklin Jameson Archival Advocacy Award / SAA", 1987-1990, undated (Box 36)
  - "Waldo Gifford Leland Prize / SAA", 1987-1990, undated (Box 36)
  - "Photography-related News Items, etc.", 1991-1995 (Box 36)
  - "Fax Machine Purchase", undated (Box 36)
  - "The Dead Sea Scrolls", 1992, 1995 (Box 36)
  - "Institut fur Kulturaustausch re: Stuttgart", 1992 (Box 36)
  - "Uptight: The Velvet Underground Story", circa 1966 (Box 36)
  - This Will Kill That material, 1978-1982, undated (Box 36)
  - "Robert Creeley", 1977-1987, undated (Box 36)
  - "David Avidan", 1978 (Box 36)
  - "Poem for Anton Pevich", 1978 June 8 (Box 36)
  - Ira Cohen material, circa 1970s-1980s; 2 (Box 36)
  - Ira Cohen material, circa 1970s-1980s; 2 (Box 37)
  - S. R. Lavin correspondence, 1979-1988; 6 (Box 37)
  - S. R. Lavin material, undated (Box 37)
  - "Peter Wehrli" material, circa 1976-1986; 3 (Box 37)
  - "Chris Peditto (Companion to Paul Grillo File)", 1983-1987; 2 (Box 37)
  - "Uptight! The Velvet Underground Story", circa 1978-1984; 4 (Box 37)
  - "Victor Bockris", 1979-1988, undated (Box 37)
  - "Joe Coplan, a/k/a Hoé", 1979-1988, undated (Box 38)
  - " This Will Kill That, Correspondence & Ephemera", 1983, undated (Box 38)
  - Sam Inglese, 1993, undated (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1991; 13 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1994, undated; 18 (Box 39)
  - "GM: Letter to David James / AWP Newsletter", undated (Box 40)
  - "GM: Copyrights / Contracts / Permissions Forms", 1969-1971 (Box 40)
  - "GM: Letter to Leslie Ullman", 1979 June 25 (Box 40)
  - "Prose Anthology Edited by G. Malanga", 1962-1981, undated (Box 40)
  - "Jonathan Kundra & Willard Maas", undated (Box 40)
  - "GM: Reading Copies", 1963-1977, undated (Box 40)
  - "Chelsea: Multimedia Issue. Gerard's Portfolio, 'Torch'", 1978, undated (Box 40)
  - "David Bourdon: 'Pop 1963' Chapter", 1987 December (Box 40)
  - "GM: One of Gerard's Earliest Prose Texts, Dating to 1960", circa 1960 (Box 40)
  - "Bennington College July Program, 1981", 1980 (Box 40)
  - Untitled material, undated (Box 40)
  - "N.E.A. Conceptual Art Project - 1984", 1983 March 20 (Box 40)
  - "Highbridge B&W Polaroid...", undated (Box 40)
  - "Ptolemy Mann (Gerard's Goddaughter)", undated (Box 40)
  - "Daddy's Little Girl (1986)...", 1984, undated (Box 40)
  - "GM: Diane Arbus Estate", 1989 February 23 (Box 40)
  - "Edward Mintur Hood: 'Last Will & Testament' Documents", 1982 (Box 40)
  - "Tonny Kinna", 1994 (Box 40)
  - "Photography Work in the Berkshires", 1990, 1994 (Box 40)
  - "Curators", 1980-1993, undated (Box 40)
  - "Archiving as Art", undated (Box 40)
  - " This Will Kill That, Page Proofs", undated (Box 40)
  - "Michael McCurdy / Penmaen Press: One of Gerard's First Publishers and Steadfast Friends", 1989-1995, undated; 4 (Box 40)
  - "Elsa Schmidt Letters When the G Lived on Anderson Street, ca. 1991", 1991-1996; 6 (Box 40)
  - "GM: The Guardian Lectures (Everything Relating to Gerard's Invitation & Visit to London, 1989)", 1989, undated; 3 (Box 41)
  - "GM: 1992 Popkomm, All Press-related to G's German & Dutch Poetry & Film Tour", 1988-1992 (Box 41)
  - "GM: Rent Receipts 1974-90. 203 East 14th Street #8, NYC 10003", circa 1974-1990; 3 (Box 41)
  - "Carl Hanni, Oregon Poet", 1994-1995, undated (Box 41)
  - "Kathleen Norris Correspondence", 1994-1996, undated (Box 41)
  - "Susan Pile / Warhol Bk Project, etc.", 1991, 1993 (Box 41)
  - "Dr. Corliss Lamont, Poet", 1980-1995, undated (Box 41)
  - "The Coffee Shop Exhibition", 1995, undated (Box 41)
  - "VYT Bakaitis, Poet", 1991 (Box 41)
  - "Marye Blonk Correspondence", 1992-1996 (Box 41)
  - "Malanga Biographical Notes, etc. Press Release Specimen Copy", 1973-1989, undated (Box 41)
  - "Paradiso - Notes to a Poem", 1994, undated (Box 41)
  - "'What Becomes a Duchamp Most?' Working Drafts", 1994, undated (Box 41)
  - "'Beyond the Nude Horizon,' Short Essay by Gerard Malanga", 1994, undated (Box 41)
  - "'Within Prior(ity),' Drafts, Gerard Malanga (1993 Dec.)", 1993 December (Box 41)
  - "'You're It,' Master Copy", 1994 June 14 (Box 41)
  - "'Seizing the Moment,' Reduction Master / 1st Draft", undated (Box 41)
  - "Bernard Mindich, Curator, The Beats, a Photo Exhibit, N.Y.U.", 1993-1994, undated (Box 41)
  - "Jim Condon / Post Mortem Productions", 1991 (Box 41)
  - "Bieke Cattoor, Belgium", 1993-1994 (Box 41)
  - "Jutta & Carsten Brandt", 1992-1996 (Box 41)
  - "Dale Davis", 1989-1995 (Box 41)
  - "Kevin Jeffrey Clarke, Poet", 1979-1990, undated (Box 41)
  - "'Three Diamonds,' Visual Material", 1988, undated (Box 41)
  - "'Three Diamonds,' Misc. & Ephemera, etc.", undated (Box 41)
  - "Rhinencephalon, Notes for 'Three Diamonds'", undated (Box 41)
  - "'Three Diamonds,' Ephemeral Materials", undated (Box 41)
  - "'Three Diamonds,' Proof Mss Copy", undated (Box 42)
  - "'Three Diamonds,' Book Party", 1991, undated (Box 42)
  - "'Three Diamonds,' Master Copy, Typescript", undated (Box 42)
  - "Working Drafts... Included in 'Three Diamonds'", 1980, undated (Box 42)
  - "'Three Diamonds,' w/ Photo-inserts", undated (Box 42)
  - "'Three Diamonds,' Duplicate Mss", undated (Box 42)
  - "'Three Diamonds,' Correspondence & Ephemera", 1988-1992, undated; 2 (Box 42)
  - " Autobiography of a Sex Thief, Mss Frag.", undated (Box 42)
  - "GM: Autobiography of a Sex Thief (1984), Bk Mss Format & Ephemera", circa 1983-1984 (Box 42)
  - "Ron Barnard, Ed: Himma", 1978, undated (Box 42)
  - "Poems Written for Gerard", circa 1964-1980 (Box 42)
  - "About Gerard Malanga", 1969-1978, undated (Box 42)
  - "Italian Subtitles Book Manuscript Format", undated (Box 42)
  - "Gerard Malanga: Mostly Tearsheets / Flyers / Announcement Cards / Ephemera", circa 1973-1985 (Box 42)
  - "Laszlo Moholy-Nagy Research File", 1983-1988, undated (Box 42)
  - "Henrik Have / Denmark", 1977-1980 (Box 42)
  - "Julia Friar, Julia Plikaitis", 1979-1986 (Box 42)
  - "'Once One Year Past,' Drafts", 1994, undated (Box 42)
  - "Untitled (Once One Year Past), Master Copy", 1994, undated (Box 42)
  - "'Writing from Memory,' Drafts", 1993, undated (Box 42)
  - "'The G and VV Story' Transcript / Mss by Ira Cohen and Gerard Malanga, Redacted by Gerard Malanga 4:x:93 from Phone Conversation 3:x:93", 1993 (Box 42)
    There is an audiocassette connected with this folder. It is located in box 113.
  - "69 Seconds into 36 Hours (1993) by Gerard Malanga & Virginia Vincent, Book Dummy for Sequencing" (Box 42)
  - "'Some Things to Remember About Tri-X,' Working Drafts", 1993, undated (Box 43)
  - " Mythologies of the Heart, Working Drafts", 1993-1994, undated (Box 43)
  - "'Things To Do in Reineke's House,' Working Drafts", 1993, undated (Box 43)
  - "Howard A Rodman, Scriptwriter", 1992-1993, undated (Box 43)
  - "'18 February 1994,' Working Drafts" (Box 43)
  - "'All the Photographs Ever Taken (Virginia Vincent),' Concept Piece", 1993, undated (Box 43)
  - "'Return to Paris After Two Years,' Working Drafts - December 1994" (Box 43)
  - "'So What Happened?' Working Drafts, 20:xii:93, by Gerard Malanga", 1993, undated (Box 43)
  - "'Farewell My Concubine,' Drafts, 18:xii:93", 1993 (Box 43)
  - "GM Tearsheets & Venues", 1990, undated (Box 43)
  - "Travelling with Duchamp Concept", 1993, undated (Box 43)
  - "Concept: Malanga Appropriation of Virginia Vincent Selfportrait Photo", undated (Box 43)
  - "Cinema Parlant ('Talking Pictures') by Gerard Malanga", 1993, undated (Box 43)
  - "Virginia Vincent Correspondence", 1993-1995, undated; 2 (Box 43)
  - "Virginia Vincent, Photographer", 1993-1994, undated; 5 (Box 43)
  - "The Legacy of Gaile Vazbys", 1983 (Box 43)
  - "Julia's First Tape to Gerard. Side 1=Letter, Readings + Annotations", undated; 1; This audiocassette is located in box 113 and considered restricted fragile. For more information, please contact Access Services. (Box 43)
  - "Julia Tape #2", 1985 October 17; 1; This audiocassette is located in box 113 and considered restricted fragile. For more information, consult Access Services. (Box 43)
  - "J to G #3", undated; 1; This audiocassette is located in box 113 and considered restricted fragile. For more information, contact Access Services. (Box 43)
  - "Julia #4", 1985 October 22; 1; This audiocassette is located in box 113 and considered restricted fragile. For more information, please contact Access Services. (Box 43)
  - "Gerard Malanga Talking to Julia Murphy, ca. Oct 16, 1985", 1985 October 16; 1; This audiocassette is located in box 113 and considered restricted fragile. For more information, please contact Access Services. (Box 43)
  - "Malanga Archival Ephemera", 1965-1971, undated (Box 44)
  - "Cooper Union - Supplement to Gaile Vazby's File", 1974-1983, undated (Box 44)
  - "Gaile Vazbys Cross-reference: Peter Wehrli, Julia Plikaitis, Andrei Codrescu", 1983 (Box 44)
  - "Gaile Vazbys", 1983-1988, undated; 2 (Box 44)
  - "Pietro Heliczer" material, 1969-1988, undated; 4 (Box 44)
  - "Julia Murphy", 1982-1989, undated; 3 (Box 44)
  - "Devotion," drafts, 1976 (Box 44)
  - "Karen Bjorson, Fashion Model", 1971-1976, undated; 2 (Box 44)
  - "GM: Arts Council of Great Britain, 1980", 1980-1981 (Box 44)
  - "Roberta Metz, Writer & Teacher", undated (Box 44)
  - "GM: Contact: Theory Ed. by Ralph Gibson, 1980", 1979, undated (Box 44)
  - "GM: Fan Letters, Inc. Vincent Katz, Todd Colby", 1978-1986 (Box 44)
  - "Lynne Tillman, Writer", undated (Box 44)
  - "Raleigh Perkins, Subject for Portrait", 1977-1981, undated (Box 44)
  - "Caila Abedon, Writer", undated (Box 45)
  - "GM: Paris Review / 25th Anniversary Issue", 1980 (Box 45)
  - "GM: Galerie von Bartha Stillborn Exhibit, 1983", 1982-1984, undated (Box 45)
  - "GM: Sarah Lawrence College Photograph Seminar Teaching Position", 1984-1985 (Box 45)
  - "GM: N.Y.U. Film Club - 1979", 1979, undated (Box 45)
  - "GM / PEN Writers Fund - 1981" (Box 45)
  - "'In Retrospect' - 1984 / GM Text", 1984 August (Box 45)
  - "Boundary / GM Photo Portfolio - 1980", 1979 (Box 45)
  - "NEA Translations Application, 1981", 1980 (Box 45)
  - "Thomas Cole Project - 1971", 1971, undated (Box 45)
  - "Guggenheim / Photography 1997 / Rejection", 1977 (Box 45)
  - "Livingston Biddle, Chairman, N.E.A., Newspaper Articles on Foundations & Grant-giving", circa 1970s-1980s (Box 45)
  - NEA and CAPS rejections, 1971-1985, undated; 17 (Box 45)
  - "CAPS Applications / Copies of Poems", undated (Box 45)
  - "Robert Francis, Poet", 1978, undated (Box 45)
  - "Paul Christensen", undated (Box 45)
  - "About Poetry, Incl. Anthony Hecht & Robert Bly", 1975-1982, undated (Box 45)
  - "NEA / Poetry 1976 Rejection (The 1st NEA Rejection)", 1975-1976 (Box 45)
  - "NEA-related Articles & Letters Involving the Big Scandal! - 1979-80", 1979-1985, undated; 2 (Box 45)
  - "Draft Proposal, MacArthur Fdn", undated (Box 45)
  - "MacArthur Foundation Proposal", 1981-1996; 3 (Box 45)
  - "Kate Lynne Morris", 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - "Barry Sternlieb / Mad River Press", 1990-1991 (Box 45)
  - "Sharon Stone, Actress", 1994 (Box 45)
  - "Guillaume Gallozzi Gallery", 1993-1994 (Box 46)
  - "Mike Gavey, Channel 4 London", 1993-1994, undated (Box 46)
  - "Govinda Gallery, Christopher Murray, Director", 1993 (Box 46)
  - "Great Barrington, Mass.", 1990-1995, undated (Box 46)
  - "Victor Bockris", 1989-1995; 2 (Box 46)
  - "Lothar Surey, Neuss Cultural Council", 1993, undated (Box 46)
  - "Penny Truex / Gordon Helman", 1990-1996; 2 (Box 46)
  - "Valerie Oisteanu, Poet", 1992-1995, undated (Box 46)
  - "David Rattray, Poet", 1987-1993, undated (Box 46)
  - "Reinhild Sander", 1992-1993 (Box 46)
  - "Timothy Baum", 1970-1995 (Box 46)
  - "The Naked Aura, 3:ii:81", 1981, undated (Box 46)
  - "Epigraphy: Exhibits & Instigations", 1974, undated; 2 (Box 46)
  - "Ira Cohen - Photocopy Collages", 1979, undated (Box 46)
  - "Kate Christen", 1985-1988, undated (Box 46)
  - "GM: Interview by Kelly Wise, 1980" (Box 46)
  - "Lindsay Faas", 1980-1984; 2 (Box 46)
  - "Ronnie Burk", 1980-1987 (Box 46)
  - "Gerard Malanga / Gay Sunshine Interview", undated (Box 46)
  - "Interview with Gerard Malanga by Bockris-Wylie", 1973 (Box 46)
  - "Becky Samsvick", 1975-1978 (Box 46)
  - "Sarah Greenleaf Whittier", 1975-1987 (Box 46)
  - "Kate Paley", 1976-1980, undated; 2 (Box 46)
  - "Elsa Schmidt" correspondence, 1992-1995, undated; 5 (Box 47)
  - "Some of the Actual Prints Used in the Book", 1961-1977, undated; 2 (Box 47)
  - "Correspondence to and from Photographers Who Didn't Participate...", 1981 (Box 47)
  - "Photovoyeurism", undated (Box 47)
  - "Questions for the Photographers", undated (Box 47)
  - "Ron Galella File", 1981-1982, undated (Box 47)
  - "Photocopies of Some of the Photos in Scopophilia ", undated (Box 47)
  - "Afterword by Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 47)
  - "Tearsheets Pertaining to Research or Relating to the Photographers in the Book", circa 1980s (Box 47)
  - "Original Transcripts w/ Photographers' Corrections and Dates of Approval and Receipt, All Signed by Malanga", 1982, undated; 2 (Box 47)
  - " Scopophilia, Correspondence and Ephemera", 1981-1986, undated (Box 47)
    These two folders are connected to two audiocassettes that can be found in box 113 under the titles, "Andy Warhol" and "Mike Donnelly" by Gerard Melanga, interviews Scopophilia.
  - " Scopophilia, Correspondence and Ephemera", 1981-1986; 3 (Box 48)
  - Notebooks, undated; 2 (Box 48)
  - "Photovoyeurism", undated (Box 48)
  - "Catalyst Mag. / Subj. Bellocq", 1988 (Box 48)
  - "GM: Texts on Eroticism & the Nude", 1984-1989, undated (Box 48)
  - Scopophilia material, 1981-1987, undated; 3 (Box 48)
  - "'Photovoyeurism,' Working Drafts w/ Marginalia and Spliced Edited Transcripts w/ Marginalia, All Signed by Malanga. Total: 27 Transcripts", 1981-1982; 2 (Box 48)
  - "'Photovoyeurism,' 1st Clean Master Copy, Incl 1st Typed Draft...", 1981-1982; 2 (Box 48)
  - "'Photovoyeurism,' Unbound Photocopy", undated (Box 49)
  - "Photovoyeurism," Final Transcripts of Eleven of the Photographers...", 1981-1982 (Box 49)
  - "The Pool Book: A 50-Year Photographic History of New York City's Public Swimming Facilities", undated (Box 49)
  - "All My Friends Are Going To Be Strangers: A Screenplay" by Larry McMurtry, 1972 (Box 49)
  - Poems, printed versions, The Coldspring Journal, 1975 (Box 49)
  - "Nine Poems for Cesar Vallejo: The Poetry of Night, Dawn and Dream," printed version, 1972 (Box 49)
  - "Liz Drives Up to Alice's Restaurant and this Is What I See," printed version, Broadway Boogie, 1975 (Box 49)
  - Radar, special issue on Malanga, 1984 (Box 49)
  - "Genealogies," printed version, Ins and Outs, 1980 (Box 49)
  - "From the Secret Diaries," printed version, Little Caesar, 1978 (Box 49)
  - "Six Poems," printed version, Lip, 1972 (Box 49)
  - "Hymn to the Volunteers of the Republic," by César Vallejo, translated by Gerard Malanga, printed version, Assassin, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Context of Poetry by Robert Creeley, review by Gerard Malanga, printed version, Granite, 1974-1975 (Box 49)
  - "The Myth of Trees," printed version, Transatlantic Review, 1975 (Box 49)
  - "Traveling & Living," printed version, Poetry, 1974 December (Box 49)
  - "GM: Autobiography of a Sex Thief ", 1982-1986 (Box 49)
  - "The Pool Book", undated (Box 49)
  - "Report from a Writers Workshop" by Rosalind Constable, 1962 July 23 (Box 49)
  - "Dress Rehearsal of an Autobiography: Photoworks 1969-1980", 1980 July (Box 49)
  - "Positively Archival" by Gerard Malanga, 1988 January 12 (Box 49)
  - "Andy's Orbit: Photos and Text" by Gerard Malanga, 1983 (Box 49)
  - "The Legacy of Gaile Vazbys", 1983 (Box 49)
  - Printed material, circa 1970s-1980s; 2 (Box 49)
  - "GM Venue: Harvard Film Society, 1991", 1991-1992, undated (Box 49)
  - "Joseph Langland Correspondence", 1992 (Box 49)
  - "The Alternative Press", undated (Box 49)
  - "Catherine Boyd Paper on A: A Novel by Andy Warhol", undated (Box 49)
  - "GM: Jack Youngerman, Painter...", 1971 (Box 50)
  - "Michael Cooper, Photographer. Also: Denis Deegan...", 1989-1990, undated (Box 50)
  - "Raymond Foye / Hanuman Books", 1991 (Box 50)
  - "GM Venue: Vincent Katz / Jack Kerouac", 1988-1996 (Box 50)
  - "Selected Obits", 1974, 1989 (Box 50)
  - "GM: Thorn T. Welden, Photography by Gerard", 1989 (Box 50)
  - "Paula Pritchett, Photographed with Paolo Lionni by Gerard", undated (Box 50)
  - "GM Venue: Lines / Detroit Inst. of Arts / George Tysh", 1988 March 16 (Box 50)
  - "GM Venue: Gallery Hirondelle / John Hersey", 1984-1986 (Box 50)
  - "Alexander Souri...", 1990-1995, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Christopher Murry / Govinda Gallery", 1989, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Downtown Community TV Center", 1988 (Box 50)
  - "Sandra Jean: Exposé Gallery Exhibit, Bethlehem, PA", 1988 (Box 50)
  - "Robert Harson, Poet", 1988 (Box 50)
  - "Harriet Zinnes, Poet", undated (Box 50)
  - "Berkshires-related", circa 1988-1992 (Box 50)
  - " Cover Arts New York, Monthly Column", 1989, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Jude Schwendenwein / Real Art Ways Exhibition Space - Hartford, CT", 1988-1990, undated (Box 50)
  - "Richard Aaron re Sale of Henry Moore Sculptures", 1988-1989, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Deirdre Goodwin Research into a Bio-feature on GM", 1982-1983, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Brad Balfour Interview Project", 1989, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Bernd Gaul / Mega Film re Velvet Underground Movie", 1987-1988 (Box 50)
  - "Robert Metz Prose Works", undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: 'The Long Poem'", 1977, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: 'The Comet Show,' 1985-86 Group Exhibit", 1985-1986 (Box 50)
  - "GM Foto Competition: China Sports", 1985 (Box 50)
  - "GM Fotos: Adrian C. Kanaar, M.D.", 1984 (Box 50)
  - "GM: Smithsonian Institution Venue, 1988", 1988, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Letter to the Editor, The NY Times re Who First Used the Silkscreen Technique", 1990-1991 (Box 50)
  - "GM: Caroline Jones PhD Dissertation - 1989" (Box 50)
  - "GM: Hayward Gallery London re Warhol Exhibit, 1989" (Box 50)
  - "GM: Art Assn of Harrisburg, PA - 1990", 1989-1990, undated (Box 50)
  - "Sara Vogeler & Dance", 1981-1982, undated (Box 50)
  - "Don Snyder: Erolumia Text", 1979, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Contracts & Copyrights", circa 1969-1985 (Box 50)
  - "GM: Research for Film Idea, 'John / Diane Delia'", 1982, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Ted Berrigan Book Review / for Cover ", 1988 (Box 50)
  - "GM: Letter to Time Mag. re Rauschenberg's Complaint re Copyright Residuals", 1974 (Box 50)
  - "Anton Perich, Video Artist", 1980, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Grant-in-Aid Assistance", 1971-1985, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: High School of Industrial Art", 1985, undated (Box 50)
  - "The Pollock-Krasner Foundation", 1985, undated (Box 50)
  - "Konglomerati Press", 1983-1984 (Box 50)
  - "GM: The Fool Bk Mss Format", 1970-1971 (Box 50)
  - "Deborah Norville", 1989, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: Poetry & Film Bookings", 1968-1969, undated (Box 50)
  - "GM: L. W. T. London Weekend Televesion re: Andy Warhol Special", circa 1985-1989 (Box 50)
  - "Bob Putnam, Editor '15 Minutes'", 1990-1992; 2 (Box 50)
  - "Bob Putnam: The Loop in Motion Festival, 1988", 1988-1992, undated; 2 (Box 50)
  - "GM: Photograph Records", 1982-1985, undated (Box 51)
  - "GM: David Ignatow Interview, Transcript / Final Version", undated (Box 51)
  - "GM: David Ignatow Introduction for Paris Review Interview, 1975", 1979 (Box 51)
  - "GM: Edwin Denby Interview, 1970", circa 1970 (Box 51)
  - "GM: Interview by David Rosenberg", undated (Box 51)
  - "GM: William Burroughs Interview. Transcript w/ Burroughs' Handwritten Copy-editing & Diane Hersey's (née Costello) Longhand Redaction", 1974, 1985 (Box 51)
  - "1996 Correspondence Time Capsule (Continuing from Parent Files)", 1992-1996, undated; 4 (Box 51)
  - "1996 Correspondence. Additional Letters", 1989-1996, undated; 3 (Box 51)
  - "1997 Correspondence Time Capsule (Continuing from Parent Files)", 1993-1997; 4 (Box 51)
  - "1997 Correspondence. Additional Letters", 1987-1997, undated; 6 (Box 52)
  - "Leonardo de Vega - Photoportraits Book...", 1994, undated (Box 52)
  - "Ronnie Burk, Poet / Collagist", 1994-1995 (Box 52)
  - "Spazi Art Gallery. Expenses for Silkscreen Mirror", 1991-1995, undated (Box 52)
  - "Wallace Berman", 1988-1990, undated (Box 52)
  - "GM: Poem for Stacey Asip, Working Drafts, 1980" (Box 52)
  - "Luman Travo - Marion van Tilborg", 1993 (Box 52)
  - "Diane Arbus", 1976-1987, undated (Box 52)
  - "Jayne H. Baum / Jayne H. Baum Gallery", 1993 February 17 (Box 52)
  - "Black Spring Press Ltd (U.K.)", 1992-1993 (Box 52)
  - "Patek Philippe, Geneve...", 1978 November 2 (Box 52)
  - "David Fahey, Fahey / Klein", 1994-1995 (Box 52)
  - "Aurore Mouliére, Correspondence", 1994-1995, undated (Box 52)
  - "Poets Grab-bag", 1986-1995; 2 (Box 52)
  - "Gabriella & Roberto Garafolo", circa 1988-1995; 2 (Box 52)
  - "Harvard University / Houghton Library", 1995-1996 (Box 52)
  - "Mechthild Hahn, Editor", 1986-1995 (Box 52)
  - "Luca Incrocci, Writer and M.D.", undated (Box 52)
  - "Ludwig Wittgenstein / Jim Jacobs from the Series Metaphoriconjunctions", 1983-1990, undated (Box 52)
  - Great Barrington, MA material, 1990-1993 (Box 52)
  - "Jerome Jacobs / Damasquine Art Gallery", 1994 April 7 (Box 52)
  - "Kevin Kushel / Photonica", 1995-1996 (Box 52)
  - "Jürgen Kisters, Koln", 1992-1993 (Box 52)
  - "Candice Perich Gallery", 1996 (Box 52)
  - "Paris Audiovisuel / Joel Brard", 1992-1994 (Box 52)
  - "Photo & Exhibit Vendors", 1987, undated (Box 52)
  - "Park Row Gallery", 1989-1993, undated (Box 52)
  - "Photo Lab Price Lists", 1994, undated (Box 53)
  - "Ine Poppe, Amsterdam", 1992-1995 (Box 53)
  - "Press Mailing List Labels", undated (Box 53)
  - "Press Release Sets", 1984-1994, undated (Box 53)
  - "Chris Pedito / Heat Press", 1992-1995, undated (Box 53)
  - "Randy Roark, Editor / Friction", 1995-1996 (Box 53)
  - "Rock & Roll Hall of Fame + Museum", undated (Box 53)
  - "Rotterdam Arts Council", 1990, 1994 (Box 53)
  - "Lothar Schirmer, Schirmer / Mosel Verlag", 1995-1996 (Box 53)
  - "Robert A. Sobieszek, Curator of Photography, Los Angeles County Museum of Art", 1995-1996 (Box 53)
  - "Aymon de Roussy de Sales", 1996 (Box 53)
  - "Jim South, Director / World Modeling", 1985 March 8 (Box 53)
  - "The Aaron Siskind Foundation, Inc.", 1989-1994, undated (Box 53)
  - "Sonnentanz-Verlag (Augsburg)", 1991-1994 (Box 53)
  - "Simons Rock", 1985-1993, undated; 2 (Box 53)
  - "Kanako Shinkado Interviews. Gerard Malanga (Tokyo, Japan) 25:iv:96", 1996 (Box 53)
  - "Dario Stipistic, Editor, Ignite", 1995-1996 (Box 53)
  - "Andy Warhol / I Shot Andy Warhol, the Film", undated (Box 53)
  - "Eileen Taft Agency / Realtor", 1996, undated (Box 53)
  - "Tetsuya Taguchi / 'Electric Rexroth' Correspondence", 1992-1994 (Box 53)
  - "Reinecke Vander Linden", 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - "Linda Shearer", 1991-1993 (Box 53)
  - "Nighttown / Warhol - Investment Capital", 1992 (Box 53)
  - "Film & Picture Research / Andy Warhol", undated (Box 53)
  - "Nighttown Productions / Miscellaneous, etc.", 1992, undated (Box 53)
  - "Nighttown Productions / Lit Agt Follow-up", 1992 March (Box 53)
  - "Nighttown Productions / Misc. Letters", 1992 (Box 53)
  - "Nighttown / Warhol - Finder's Fee Letters", 1992 March (Box 53)
  - "Libido / Journal of Sex & Sensibility", 1992-1995; 3 (Box 53)
  - "Le Sept / Video - Marianne Levy-Leblond", 1994 June (Box 53)
  - "Video-biography / Gerard Malanga & Daniel Mangeon", 1995-1996 (Box 53)
  - "GM: European Film Tour", 1990-1991, undated; 2 (Box 53)
  - "Model Announcement Masters", 1990, undated (Box 54)
  - "Archives Malanga", 1991, undated (Box 54)
  - "Malanga Film Programme - Master Copy", 1990-1993 (Box 54)
  - "Pete Madden, Amsterdam", 1992-1996, undated (Box 54)
  - "Malanga Biography Project by Debra Miller w/ Gerard Malanga", 1994-1996 (Box 54)